Mr Zeth
Why are you buying frogs yourself
BossLewes raises high-quality frogs
They're worth a trip
What are you doing
Trying to compete with me
No no
We wouldn't dare compete with you
Exactly
Who doesn't know Mr Zeth from Harian Group
Is Forestwood
Top boss in the purchasing industry
We aren't even fit to tie your shoes
We wouldn't dare steal your business
Mr Zeth
We'll leave you to it
We're leaving now
We won't hold you up
Pay the compensation
within three days
Or I'll break your legs
After you Mr Zeth
Let me be clear upfront
My standards are very high
If they aren't as good as you promised
I won't buy a single one
Alright
Great frogs
Oh my god
Such big frogs
I've never seen anything like them
Huge
Plump
Top-notch appearance
I've been in this industry for 20 years
And I've never seen such good quality
Look at the frogs Lewes raises
All plump and strong
This is real skill
Yeah
Then look at Daniel's frogs over there
Small and skinny
And covered in sores
I wouldn't take them for free
Damn it
Such great frogs
Why aren't they mine
Boss Lewes
This batch of your frogs
At the highest market price
I'll take them all
Here's 3.2 million
From now on your frogs
I'll buy them all at the highest market price
Zane
Get out here